Hey boy
Look, I’m gonna make this simple for you.
You got two choices…
YES or YES?
Ah choose only one of the two YES or YES?
Ah ah make your choice come on YES or YES?
Since when was I so selfish?
Did I ever want something this eagerly?
Everyone is surprised at
how shameless I am
Come on and tell me yes
My scenario has become
more daring than I thought
I’d say this plan is perfect, quite satisfying
I don’t care no matter what others say
You better tell me yes
I have decided YES!
Now it’s time to hear your answer
If it’s too hard,
there are examples to choose from
You don’t have to waste your time thinking
Don’t know what you’ll choose,
so I prepared these options
Choose only one of the two YES or YES?
Don’t know what you want,
so I prepared these options
Make your choice come on YES or YES?
I will say no to your no, is it me or us?
I respect your choice
but reject your rejection
There is only one answer,
the choice is up to you
It’s all up to you
Choose only one of the two YES or YES?
Do you mean it? Do not guess
Are you serious? Do not ask
Don’t give me that unsure side-to-side,
I want a sure up-and-down
There’s no letters N & O
I’ll erase them from today
There’s no need to think too hard
The answer is YES YES YO
You bring out my hidden selfishness
Your eyes and
my curiosity about you
make my heart burning
My heart burn burn burn
You better hurry up
To make it simple
Whatever you choose, you will be with me
Though it may seem a bit absurd
Though you might say I’m insisting you
I’ll make you to never regret
Don’t know what you’ll choose,
so I prepared these options
Choose only one of the two YES or YES?
Don’t know what you want,
so I prepared these options
Make your choice come on YES or YES?
I will say no to your no, is it me or us?
I respect your choice
but reject your rejection
There is only one answer,
the choice is up to you
Now, it’s all up to you
Maybe not
No! No!
Maybe yes
Make it more clearly
Show me how you feel
Open your ears. Don’t you hear it?
It's! Simple! Y! E! S! Hey!
Choose only one of the two YES or YES?
Make your choice come on YES or YES?
Here is one more YES or YES or YES
Take your pick, the choice is up to you
Don’t know what you’ll choose,
so I prepared these options
Choose only one of the two YES or YES?
Don’t know what you want,
so I prepared these options
Make your choice come on YES or YES?
I will say no to your no, is it me or us?
I respect your choice
but reject your rejection
There is only one answer,
the choice is up to you
It’s all up to you
Make your choice come on YES or YES?